palmettobluff.com 2015-04-23

# Privacy Policy - Palmetto

**  Equal Housing Opportunity.**  
Crescent Communities, LLC's (hereinafter "Crescent Communities") Privacy Policy ("Policy") sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it. Please contact us at 227 W. Trade Street, Suite 1000, Charlotte, NC 28202, or by phone at (980) 321-6000, or through our web site located at [www.crescentcommunities.com/contact.asp](http://166.78.48.146:9009/www.crescentcommunities.com/contact.asp) if you have any questions or would like additional information regarding this Policy. We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check this Policy periodically for changes.

**Your Information**  
As a company that provides land management, commercial and residential services, we may collect non-public, personal information directly from our customers and visitors to our web site, including when visitors submit information through our web site located at [www.crescent-resources.com](http://166.78.48.146:9009/www.crescent-resources.com) and/or our website located at [www.palmettobluff.com](http://166.78.48.146:9009/www.palmettobluff.com) and/or our website located at [www.palmettobluff.com](http://166.78.48.146:9009/www.palmettobluff.com). We define "personal information" as information that is unique to an individual and might include the following: name, contact information, email addresses, and telephone numbers. We will update your information whenever we can to keep it current, accurate and complete.

**Our Use of Your Information**  
If we do receive your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected, and we will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of Crescent Communities unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us, (3) in order to provide our services to you (and contacting you when necessary), (4) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements, (5) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Crescent Communities or the merger of Crescent Communities into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Crescent Communities is not the survivor, (6) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, customer care, service quality, business management and operation, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection, or (7) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information (whether collected online or offline) with third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section of this Policy.

If you do not agree to Our Use of Your Information above, please do not use our web site or submit your personal information to us. Your continued use of our web site constitutes your acceptance of this Policy.

**Contests, Sweepstakes and Other Promotions**  
On our web site, you may wish to participate in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time. Through these promotions, you may choose to participate in activities such as sharing information found on our web site with others and sending email invitations. If you choose to participate in these promotions, and are eligible to do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, date of birth and telephone number.

In connection with any contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time via the web site, we use the information you provide to administer the contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we also may use the information to communicate with you, or the other people you select, about our services or our partners may use such information to communicate with you about the contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services. In connection with such contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, we will not use information you provide about other people for any purpose except the purpose you direct without first getting their consent. 

**Direct Marketing Material**  
Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we may from time to time contact you with information on offers of goods and services, brochures, new products, and forthcoming events. Our web site will assume you to agree to electronic communications when you request services online. You may indicate your preference regarding receiving third party direct marketing material. If do not wish to receive such information or would like to change your preference, please refer to "Your Rights: below. Contacting Us Regarding Your Questions and Comments We appreciate your questions and comments about Crescent Communities and its services and welcome you to send us your comments or questions through our web site, by phone or mail as described in How to Contact Us section below. We will share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it once it is no longer needed. 

**Your Rights**  
You have the right to ask in writing not to receive direct marketing material from us. If available, you can amend your previous preferences by contacting us through our web site, by phone or mail as described in How to Contact Us section below or refer to our literature containing instructions. Once properly notified by you, we will take steps to stop using your information in this way. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request. 

**Use of Tools, "Cookies" and Links to Other Web sites**  
If our contact and dealing with you is via our web site(s), we may use "cookies". Cookies allow us to identify your computer, but not you personally. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to enjoy access and use all of the content available to you on our web site.

However, if you also receive our email marketing, we may tailor the information we send you unless you to tell us not to. This means we may use information we hold and cookies to identify your individual web site search behavior and preferences. This will enable us to send you more personalized and relevant communications. You will be given the opportunity on every communication to opt-out of this personalization. We collect information relating to customer trends and patterns and use cookies and software tools to measure site usage and related information. In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we may also obtain information which you provide to us online - for example, when you sign up for service updates, contact us regarding land management, residential or commercial services, or otherwise communicate with us. In other cases, we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our web site, we may view the IP address (which may include the city, domain address and service provider) of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our web site visitors come. We also may use this information to enhance our web site.

Certain pages on our web site contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

**Children**  
We are committed to preserving online privacy for all of the visitors to our web site, including children. Our web site is a general audience web site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or provide services to children. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. This web site is not designed to attract anyone under the age of 18.

**Monitoring**  
To ensure that we carry out your instructions accurately, improve our services and for security, we may monitor and/or record: (1) telephone calls; (2) activities using CCTV in and around our premises; and (3) transactions and activities on our web site. All recordings are and shall remain our sole property.

**Security Statement**  
We have taken all reasonable steps and have in place appropriate security measures to protect your personal information, including keeping your financial information private and safe. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our best efforts. Thus, while we will use every means possible to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

**Visiting Our Website from Outside the United States**  
If you are visiting our web site or purchasing our services from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using or purchasing our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.

**Changes to this Policy**  
We may change this Policy at any time and from time to time. Any changes to this Policy will be either posted on our web site, brochure and/or made available on request. The most recent version of the Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Policy. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party. 

**Links to Other Web sites**  
For your convenience, we may provide links to other web sites and web pages that we do not control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any web sites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these web sites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please write to us at Crescent Communities, LLC, 227 W. Trade Street, Suite 1000, Charlotte, NC 28202, or by phone at (980) 321-6000, or through our web site located at <http://www.crescentcommunities.com/contact-us/>.

Privacy Policy: last updated June 29, 2011.
